savorjapan.com 2017-03-22

# Privacy policy SAVOR JAPAN -Japanese Restaurant Guide-

## Privacy policy

We as a company have a deep recognition of the importance of the personal information of users in our corporate activities, which focus on music distribution and also include ICT and advertising support activities, and have established the following policy in order that our customers may have peace of mind in the use of our services.

  * 1\. We comply with all laws and regulations, national guidelines and other norms in the handling of personal information, and personal information is acquired, used and provided within usage guidelines and within the scope required for the business activities of our company, except where otherwise set out by law, and measures are in place to prevent use for any other purposes.
  * 2\. We take all reasonable measures, corrective measures and preventive measures on technical and organizations levels against the risk of the leakage, loss or damage to personal information or the unauthorized access of personal information.
  * 3\. In order to ensure that personal information is used appropriately and that it is protected, a clear personal information protection management system is in place, and officers and employees are thoroughly aware of this system and continuous reviews and improvements are carried out to ensure compliance. In addition, business partners are requested to handle personal information appropriately, and strive to protect personal information.
  * 4\. Our company has established personal information contact representatives for receiving requests from users themselves regarding the disclosure, correction, deletion or suspension of use of personal information held by the company, and for receiving other complaints or queries in this regard.

USEN Corporation  
Chief Executive Officer, President and Representative Director  
Kimimasa Tamura

Established March 1, 2005  
Revised November 16, 2007  
Revised November 8, 2010  
Revised December 1, 2013
